https://fourmanindustries.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use | Fourman Industries
Custom Color, Custom Print Extension Cords. Unbeatable prices, fast shipping. Call 1-800-424-8150
Extension Cords by Color
Black Extension CordsBlue Extension CordsGreen Extension CordsOrange Extension CordsPink Extension CordsPurple Extension CordsRed Extension CordsWhite Extension CordsYellow Extension Cords
Extension Cords by Length
15-foot Extension Cords25-foot Extension Cords50-foot Extension Cord100-foot Extension Cords
Heavy Duty Extension Cords by Gauge
10 Gauge12 Gauge14 Gauge
Convention Extension Cord
12 GAUGE SPT-3 Flat Convention Cord- Black 100'12 GAUGE SPT-3 Flat Convention Cord- Black 15'12 Gauge SPT-3 Flat Convention Cord- WHITE 25'12 Gauge SPT-3 Flat Convention Cord-Black 75'
Jobsite Temporary LightstringsAdaptors and Accessories
Power Tools and Consumables
Drill Bit SetsHSS "Jobber" Drill BitsMasonry Drill BitsPower ToolsSaw Blades & Hole Saws
Circular Saw BladesDiamond Saw BladesReciprocating Saw BladesBi-metal Hole SawsHole Saw AccessoriesHole Saw Kits
Abrasives
Safety & Protection
Home > Terms of Use
Terms of Use
The Fourman Industries Web Site (“Site”) owned and operated by Fourman Industries (“Fourman Industries”), consisting of company information, services and proprietary content, links, search capabilities and other Internet resources provided by Fourman Industries, affiliates of Fourman Industries and third parties. The terms, conditions and notices below (“Terms of Use”) govern your use of this Site. Your use of this Site constitutes your agreement to these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with these Terms of Use, please do not use this site. Fourman Industries reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these Terms of Use at any time. These Terms of Use were last updated November 2, 2009. Please check this page periodically for any modifications.
Copyright, Patent, and Trademark Notice
All contents in this Site, including, without limitation, Site layout, functionalities, design, text, images, graphics, documents, data files, video and audio content (“Contents”) are the property of Fourman Industries, its affiliated companies or licensors and are protected by international copyright, patent, and trademark laws. You may not publish, copy, display, distribute, transmit, perform, modify, create derivative works from, or sell any Contents, information, products, or services obtained from this Site, except as otherwise expressly permitted under applicable law and as described in these Terms of Use. Fourman Industries retains all right, title, and interest to the Contents. Except as permitted by applicable laws, you are prohibited from using any of the marks appearing on this Site without express written consent from the respective trademark owners.
Use of and Downloading Contents
Fourman Industries grants you permission to print or download Contents on the Site so long as the Contents (i) is solely for informational use or for permitted commercial uses in support of the Fourman Industries’ products, services, or business interests and is not modified or revised in any manner; (ii) plainly displays all copyright, trademark, trade name, service mark, or any other proprietary notices or legends, in the same form and manner as on the original; and (iii) displays a statement that the Contents are used solely with permission of the Fourman Industries. You may not engage in systematic retrieval of data or other Contents from this site to create or compile, directly or indirectly, a collection, compilation, database, or directory without written permission from Fourman Industries. Nor may you mirror on your own site the home page or results pages of this Site. Use of the Contents on this Site for any purpose not expressly permitted in these Terms of Use is prohibited.
If you (or a legal entity you control) own and operate a Web site or engage in other Internet activity, such as electronic commerce, communication, publishing and transmission, and want to download, post, publish, or use Contents for any such Web site or Internet activity, you will need permission from Fourman Industries, even though your Web site or Internet activity is free of charge.
Privacy Policy
Certain personal information about you is subject to our Privacy Policy. For more information, see our full Privacy Policy.
Third-Party Sites
This Site provides links to other Web Sites or resources for your convenience. Fourman Industries has selected these resources as having some value and pertinence, but their development and maintenance are not under the direction of Fourman Industries. Thus, the content, accuracy, and suitability of information contained therein, opinions expressed therein, and other links provided by these resources are neither monitored nor reviewed by Fourman Industries.
You acknowledge and agree that Fourman Industries is not responsible for the availability of such external Web Sites or resources, and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources and shall not be liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused by the use of any such content, product, or materials. You access, use, and rely upon such content, products, or materials at your own risk.
Linking to the Site
Any party seeking to publish any link to this Site on another Web Site should notify Fourman Industries in advance of any such link. Any linking to the Site shall be at your own risk and expense and shall not be construed as an endorsement by or implication of any affiliation with Fourman Industries, unless Fourman Industries authorizes such linking in advance. Fourman Industries reserves the right to object to or have removed any link that is determined by Fourman Industries in its sole judgment to be inappropriate, inconsistent with the Site’s image and reputation, or otherwise creates an undue burden on the Site or on Fourman Industries.
Co-branding and Framing
You may not, nor may you authorize any other person to, (i) co-brand the Site or portion thereof (whereby you display a name, logo, trademark, or other means of identification of any party in such a manner that gives a user the impression that such other party has the right to display, publish, or distribute the Site or Material accessible with the Site), or (ii) frame the Site or portion thereof (whereby the Site or portion thereof will appear on the same screen with a portion of another Site). Fourman Industries’ consent must be obtained in before framing, co-branding, or other activity impacting the access to or the use of this Site. Failure to obtain such consent may result in an infringement claim or other legal action being brought. You agree to cooperate with Fourman Industries in causing any unauthorized framing, co-branding, or other activity impacting the access to or the use of our Site to immediately cease.
Disclaimer of Warranty
THE SITE AND ALL INFORMATION AND OTHER CONTENT (INCLUDING THIRD-PARTY INFORMATION, PRODUCTS, AND CONTENT) INCLUDED IN OR ACCESSIBLE FROM THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND FOURMAN INDUSTRIES DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, AND STATUTORY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF TITLE AND NONINFRINGEMENT AND THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
Neither Fourman Industries, its affiliates, nor any third-party content providers or licensors makes any warranty whatsoever, including without limitation (i) that defects will be corrected; (ii) that the Site and the server it resides in, is free of viruses, worms, Trojan Horses, or other harmful components and/or code that manifest contaminating or destructive properties; and (iii) to the accuracy, reliability, availability, suitability, quality, or operation of the Site and any information, or service provided on or accessible from the Site. In addition, Fourman Industries does not assume any responsibility or risk for your use of the Internet.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL FOURMAN INDUSTRIES, ITS DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, AFFILIATES, AGENTS, AND LICENSORS, OR CONTENT PROVIDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING LOSS OR REVENUE OR INCOME, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, OR SIMILAR DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, AUTHORIZED USE, PERFORMANCE, OR NONPERFORMANCE OF THIS SITE, EVEN IF FOURMAN INDUSTRIES WAS PREVIOUSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES AND REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUCH DAMAGES ARISE IN CONTRACT, TORT, UNDER STATUTE, IN EQUITY, AT LAW, OR OTHERWISE.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify and hold Fourman Industries, its directors, officers, affiliates, agents, and licensors harmless from and against all losses, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from your violation of these Terms of Use, including without limitation, any use of Contents other than as expressly authorized by these Terms of Use.
Governing Law
These Terms of Use are governed by the laws of the United States and the State of California, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws.
Copyrights
All contents of this Site are © 2009 Fourman Industries or its licensors. All rights reserved. Photographs and illustrations are copyrighted by their respective owners, as noted in the credits.
InformationAbout Us
Contact Us
Distributor Inquiries
Shipping Information
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Get in Touch
1-800-424-8150 1-800-424-8623 info@fourmanindustries.com
Already a customer? Login to your account.
Fourman Industries | All Rights Are Reserved.
